gettyimages.com.mx 2015-12-28

# Getty Images Latin America Privacy Policy

Getty Images Latin America (Spain), S.L. and all of its subsidiaries and affiliates (jointly "Getty Images Latin America") are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy tells you about our online collection and use of data. The terms of this policy apply to all Getty Images Latin America websites, unless different terms are specified in a form or contract provided to you online or offline. In the event of any contradiction between the terms of this Agreement and the terms in any other privacy form or contract provided to you online or offline, the terms of this policy shall prevail.

By using this site, you understand and agree to the terms of this policy. This site is owned by Getty Images Latin America and may be accessed in various countries around the world. For data protection purposes, Getty Images Latin America is the controller and, unless otherwise noted, is also the processor of data. Information collected may be retained, and may be stored, processed, accessed, and used in any jurisdiction including those whose privacy laws may be different and less protective than those of your home jurisdiction.

####  Collection of Your Personal Information

When you visit this site, certain kinds of information, such as the website that referred you to us, your IP address, browser type and language, and access times, may be collected automatically as part of the site's operation. We also may collect navigational information, including information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions taken in connection with the site.

We may combine your visit and navigational information with personal information that you provide. You may always choose not to provide personal information, but if you so choose, certain products and services may not be available to you. Personal information (e.g., your username and password, your name, your mailing address, email address, and phone number) is collected when you register. Additional personal information (e.g., your credit card number and billing address) is collected to process transactions or to provide you with products and services.

Demographic information (e.g., your age, hobbies, income, gender, or interests) may also be collected and may be linked to your personal information.

####  Use of Your Personal Information

Getty Images Latin America collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve our sites, to process your transactions, to provide customer service, to perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies, and to display content that is customized to your interests and preferences.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. By providing your personal information you allow us to send tou transaction-related communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, and purchase confirmations, as well as surveys or marketing communications to inform you of new products or services or other information that may be of interest. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications, you may adjust your "Personal Information Preferences" as described below or follow the "unsubscribe" instructions included within each email communication. Please keep in mind that, if you choose not to receive marketing communications, you will continue to receive transactional or account communications (e.g., confirmation emails and account balance statements).

Personal information collected by Getty Images Latin America may be stored and processed in any other country in which Getty Images Latin America or its affiliates, subsidiaries, contractors or agents maintain facilities, and by using our sites or services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. If you would like to exercise any of your data protection rights under any of the applicable laws to your jurisdiction/domicile (including the right to have your personal information deleted), please contact us using the "Contact Information" below.

####  Sharing of Your Personal Information

Except as disclosed in this privacy policy, Getty Images Latin America does not share your personal information with any outside parties.

We may share your personal information within our corporate group, including with our subsidiaries and affiliates, all of whom may use your information for the purposes disclosed herein. We may also share your personal information with Getty Images, Inc., including its subsidiaries and affiliates and other members of its corporate group. If any other company acquires Getty Images Latin America, we may share your personal information with the acquiring company and other members of their corporate group.

You agree that we may share your personal information with service providers who perform services on our behalf. For example, we may hire other companies to handle the processing of payments, to provide data storage, to host websites, to fulfill orders and shipments, to assist in direct marketing, to conduct audits, etc. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to provide the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

Information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, or sale of the company and/or its assets, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. We will notify you of such an occurrence as described in the "Changes to This Privacy Policy" section below.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or protect the rights, property or safety of our company, employees, customers, or the public.

If you obtain a license of copyrighted photographs of the National Basketball Association, Women's National Basketball Association, National Basketball Development league or any of their respective affiliates (collectively, the "NBA Parties"), you agree that your personal information may be shared with the NBA Parties, their affiliated entities and business partners, and used for their commercial activities, including marketing. Please see the "Personal Information Preferences" section below for instructions on how you can revoke your consent to have your information shared with the NBA Parties.

####  Accessing Your Personal Information

If you would like to review or revise information that you previously provided to us, you may access your information in the "My Account" section of the website. Your sales representative can also assist you in making any changes, as well as in exercising your right to have your personal information deleted. If you need additional assistance, please contact us at infola@gettyimageslatam.com. You can expect a response from us within 10 calendar days. Please be advised that you cannot change your username without re-registering.

####  Personal Information Preferences

Getty Images Latin America respects your right to make choices about the use and disclosure of your personal information. If at any time you decide that you do not want to receive marketing communications from us, please let us know by: (1) checking or un-checking the appropriate box on your online registration form or the "My Profile" page of the website; (2) contacting your Account Executive; or (3) sending an email to infola@gettyimageslatam.com. Please note that we make take some time to implement your decision and to stop sending you marketing communications, although we will use our reasonable efforts to do this as soon as possible.

If you choose not to receive marketing communications, please be advised that you will continue to receive transactional or account communications (e.g., confirmation emails and account balance statements).

If you are a licensee of copyrighted photographs of the NBA Parties and would like to revoke your consent to have your information shared with the NBA Parties, you may express that preference by contacting your Account Executive or by sending an email to infola@gettyimageslatam.com.

####  Use of Cookies and Other Technologies

Getty Images Latin America uses "cookie" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive. Cookies contain information, including personal information, that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit, your registration information, and your navigational and purchase history.

Cookies offer you many conveniences. They allow us to identify registered users when they return to the site so that they can retrieve previous image search results, access Lightboxes and Clipbins and view their previous invoices. Cookies also save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information.

In some cases, our third-party service providers may use cookies on our sites. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Getty Images Latin America or any by its corporate group including subsidiaries and divisions, only, and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies.

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies, including single-pixel gifs (also known as web beacons) on our websites and in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters. These tiny electronic images assist us in determining how many users have visited certain pages or opened messages or newsletters. We do not use these images to collect personal information.

####  Security of Your Personal Information

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to help protect your personal information. For instance, when you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If a password is used to protect your account and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential.

####  Forums & Other Interactive Services

Our websites may include discussion forums or other interactive areas or services, including blogs, chat rooms, bulletin boards, message boards, online hosting or storage services, or other areas or services in which you or third parties create, post or store any content, messages, comments, materials or other items on the sites ("Interactive Areas"). If you use an Interactive Area, you should be aware that these areas are open to the public and any personal information you post or provide at registration may be viewable by others. We are not responsible for personal information you submit in connection with the Interactive Areas, nor are we responsible for how others might use that information (which may include sending you unsolicited messages). Interactive Area postings may be retained indefinitely. If at any time you would like to remove a posting, please email us at sales@gettyimages.com. Keep in mind that removal of a posting from an Interactive Area does not mean that the posting will be deleted from our systems.

####  Email Referrals

If you choose to use our email referral services to tell a friend about our products or services (including images in your Lightbox, promotional campaigns, new websites, job postings, etc.), we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will use that information to send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site and review the product or service you have selected. We may use a third-party provider to administer this function, but any such third party provider may only use the information submitted to facilitate this one-time email. Neither Getty Images Latin America nor any third-party provider stores this information after the email is sent.

####  Children

We do not intend to solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18 or under the age considered lawful under the laws of your jurisdiction/domicile. If you are under such age, you should not use or enter information on this site, including without limitation, any Interactive Areas of the site.

####  Links

We may link to websites, including those of our third-party content providers, that have different privacy policies and practices from those disclosed here. We assume no responsibility for the policies or practices of such linked sites, and encourage you to become acquainted with them prior to use.

####  DMA

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should first contact Getty Images (using the Contact Information below). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry, or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact the Direct Marketing Association by e-mail at "safeharbor@the-dma.org", by mail at "Safe Harbor Line, Direct Marketing Association, 1615 L Street, NW - Suite 1100, Washington, DC 20036, USA", or by phone at +1-202-861-2410.]

####  Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. When we make changes, we will revise the "last updated" date at the bottom of the policy. If there are material changes to this statement or in how Getty Images Latin America will use your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes here or on our home page, or by sending you an email. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit one of our sites.

####  Contact Information

You can contact Getty Images Latin America Sales by emailing infola@gettyimageslatam.com, or by phone at +55.5004.0430, or by postal mail at Getty Images Latin America (Spain), S.L., c/o Larrauri & Martí Abogados, Calle Hermosilla, 30 - 3º, 28001 Madrid, Spain. Alternatively, you may call or contact by postal mail your local Getty Images Latin America office using the contact details provided elsewhere on this website.

Last updated: September 2009
